# Adam J. Stevenson

425.786.3221 C • adamscdcm@gmail.com • Seattle, WA 98166

#### **Objective**

Obtain a challenging position as a front end web developer where I can continue to grow and deepen my Web Development knowledge and experience. As a newly trained student of a full stack web development bootcamp, I am eager to learn more and continue to develop my skills. My goal is to join a progressive team where I can offer my knowledge and gain more experience. I am a professional with many years of team building and managing, I have the ability to connect with people, build relationships and contribute to problem solving- key factors needed in my new career path as a Web Developer.

What I look forward to most is the opportunity to deepen my skills, build relationships and satisfy my curiosity to figuring out how things work!

#### Education

#### Full Stack Web Development University of Washington Full Stack Web Dev Bootcamp

December 2020-June 2021

### Recent Web Dev Projects

<u>WatchNext</u> The application helps the user choose a movie or series over multiple services based on their preferences by retrieving data from [movie API].

Languages/Technologies JavaScript, Jquery, Bulma, API, Figma

https://adams1971.github.io/WatchNext/

JavaScript Quiz A simple JavaScript Multiple Choice Quiz to Test Your Knowledge

Languages/Technologies JavaScript, Jquery, CSS

https://adams1971.github.io/javascript--quiz/

<u>Weather Dashboard</u> A weather application using an API that will display users searched cities current weather conditions and five day forecasts.

Languages/Technologies JavaScript, Jquery, Bootstrap, API

https://adams1971.github.io/Weather-Dashboard/

#### **Professional Experience**

#### Cedarbrook Lodge 18525 36<sup>th</sup> Ave S. Seattle WA 98188

February 2018 - Present

Executive Chef

Responsible for all aspects of the culinary operation, with special focus on Copperleaf Restaurant & Copperleaf Terrace.

<u>Cedarbrook's Fine Dining</u> flagship dining room. Focusing on Seasonal & Local Fare creating multiple course experiences from chef tasting menus to an la carte and prefix service.

Overseeing the hotel's banquet kitchen, 20000sqft capacity also preparing experiences that are "Ad Hoc" in approach changing several menus daily.

Director of all kitchen functions through the management of the culinary leadership team consisting of a Chef de Cuisine, Banquet Chef and Lead Cook Supervisors cook level cooking brigade.

#### Motif Seattle Hotel, Frol!k Kitchen & Cocktails, 4415 5th Ave, Seattle WA. 98101

April 2014- December 2017

Executive Chef

## Pro Sports Club, 4455 148<sup>th</sup> Ave NE, Bellevue WA. 98007

September 2011- April 2014

Executive Chef.

### W Hotel Seattle, 1112 Fourth Avenue, Seattle WA 98101

August 2001 - March 2011

Award winning 4-diamond hotel and 'Earth & Ocean Restaurant and W Bar'

Executive Chef • September 2006- March 2011

### Tulio Restaurant, 1100 Fifth Avenue, Seattle WA 98101, 206.624.5500 (Hotel Vintage Park)

January 1993 - January 2001

Executive Sous Chef

Side Projects

# Cascade Dry Cured Meats

2007- Present

Creator and developer of artisan dry cured meats and salami

### NuTiger Organics Catering Cascadia, Burien WA

March 2012 - Present

Co-Owner/Operator

Producer of raw organic cashew milk & Private Catering upon request

GitHub: https://github.com/adams1971 Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/adam-stevenson-sea/